## **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Vikram Singh

Hno 256/14 Nanak nagar JAMMU Pin Code 180001 Mobile No: 09469746777

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To take up an assignment that offers wide scope of learning and helps me to develop myself as a working professional so I can contribute in the knowledge industry as well as the corporate sector. A challenging career to grow, learn and to utilize the Experience and the knowledge acquired to deliver a highly professional standard of work.

#### **EDUCATIONAL PROFILE**

- ► 10<sup>th</sup> from JK Board School Education
- ▶ 12<sup>th</sup> from JK Board School Education
- B.A from Jammu University

## **ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATION**

> Two year computersdiploma

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

- ➤ Workedwith FrancoIndianpharmaceutical from year 2012 to 2017
- ➤ Worked with Jagsonpal pharmaceuticals from 2017 to 2019
- working with Chem med pharmaceuticals from year 2019 till date

#### PERSONAL STRENGTH:

➤ Being a good Listener I am able to maintain a good relationship with other. I have a great deal of trust and faith in life and failure

do not crust my spirit. I am quick Learner that helps me to understand the things quickly. I have comprehensive skills that help me to tackle the situation effectively

## **PERSONAL DETAILS:**

Name :	Vikram singh
--------	--------------

Date of Birth : 16/04/1986

Nationality : Indian

Languages Known : English, Hindi, Kashmiri and Dogri

Gender : Male

Marital status : Married

Religion : Sikh

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

- ➤ Hardworking
- **▶** Ambitious
- ➤ Helpful and Dedicated

## **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that all the details furnished above are true to the best of my knowledge. With Regards

Date	Signature:
------	------------

